As developers, we fear working with legacy code because it is difficult to understand,
作为开发人员，我们担心使用遗留代码，因为它很难理解，
modify, or extend.
修改或扩展。
The good part is, you can refactor your code bases to improve its design or structure.
好消息是，您可以重构代码库以改善其设计或结构。
I know, we avoid refactoring because it can break our existing code.
我知道，我们避免重构，因为它会破坏我们现有的代码。
In this screen cast, we'll look at how IntelliJ IDEA can help you to refactor your code safely,
在此屏幕截图中，我们将研究IntelliJ IDEA如何帮助您安全地重构代码，
with extract variable refactorings.
提取变量重构。
We'll also talk about some of the dos and don'ts because refactoring is not a magic
我们还将讨论一些注意事项，因为重构不是魔术
bullet.
子弹。
In this code, lets extract the highlight expression to a variable.
在此代码中，让我们将突出显示表达式提取到变量中。
You can use the shortcut keys Control-Alt-V on a windows system or Command-Alt-V on a
您可以在Windows系统上使用快捷键Control-Alt-V或在Windows上使用Command-Alt-V
Mac.
苹果电脑。
Depending on your context, IntelliJ IDEA suggests a default name for the extracted variable,
根据您的上下文，IntelliJ IDEA会为提取的变量建议一个默认名称，
which you can change.
您可以更改。
You can choose to define this variable as final or by using var.
您可以选择将此变量定义为final或使用var。
For this example, I'll choose both of them.
在此示例中，我将选择两者。
Option to use var during extraction is new to IntelliJ IDEA 2019.1.
提取期间使用var的选项是IntelliJ IDEA 2019.1的新增功能。
Also var was added in Java 10.
Java 10中也添加了var。
So you should configure project language level to 10+ in IntelliJ IDEA - which is available
因此，您应该在IntelliJ IDEA中将项目语言级别配置为10+。
with JDKs 10 or higher).
JDK 10或更高版本）。
By extracting a part of the expression into a new variable, the original expression is
通过将表达式的一部分提取到新变量中，原始表达式为
easy to read and follow now.
易于阅读并立即关注。
Now let's work with a comparatively complex example, which uses current date and time
现在让我们来看一个比较复杂的示例，该示例使用当前日期和时间
to return a unique string in a predefined format.
以预定义的格式返回唯一的字符串。
Most of the work is being done here by the return statement.
这里的大部分工作都由return语句完成。
It concatenates a string value and date time components.
它连接字符串值和日期时间部分。
However, over time, it might become difficult to follow all this logic.
但是，随着时间的流逝，可能很难遵循所有这些逻辑。
So, lets simplify this expression by extracting its parts to variables.
因此，让我们通过将其部分提取为变量来简化该表达式。
Select the String literal "J" and extract it to variable 'prefix'.
选择字符串文字“ J”并将其提取到变量“前缀”。
Now select the expression that extracts year for LocalDateTime instance.
现在，选择提取LocalDateTime实例的年份的表达式。
IntelliJ IDEA suggests an appropriate name.
IntelliJ IDEA建议使用合适的名称。
Now, lets extract the highlighted expression to a variable.
现在，让我们将突出显示的表达式提取到变量中。
This expression returns month using two digits.
该表达式使用两位数字返回月份。
For months that have a single digit, it prefixes them with zero.
对于只有一位数字的月份，其前缀为零。
Let's extract this expression to a variable too.
让我们也将此表达式提取到变量中。
Let's rearrange the modified expression to see how easy it has become to read and follow.
让我们重新排列修改后的表达式，以查看它变得易于阅读和遵循。
IntelliJ IDEA is quick to detect if the expression that you are extracting to another variable
IntelliJ IDEA可以快速检测您要提取的表达式是否为另一个变量
is duplicated in multiple places.
在多个地方重复。
If it is, it offers to replace one or all occurrences of the selected expression.
如果是这样，它可以替换一个或所有出现的所选表达式。
You can also change the default variable name suggested by IntelliJ IDEA.
您还可以更改IntelliJ IDEA建议的默认变量名称。
You can find complex expressions in various places, like a field initializer.
您可以在各个地方找到复杂的表达式，例如字段初始化器。
With IntelliJ IDEA 2019.1, you can also use extract refactoring with complex expressions
借助IntelliJ IDEA 2019.1，您还可以对复杂的表达式使用提取重构
in field initializers.
在字段初始化程序中。
Interestingly, the Java compiler also moves the initialization code from your field declaration
有趣的是，Java编译器还将移动代码从字段声明中移出
to instance initializers.
实例初始化器。
IntelliJ IDEA 2019.1 can convert ternary operators to if-else statements in select cases.
IntelliJ IDEA 2019.1可以在某些情况下将三元运算符转换为if-else语句。
As developers, we would need it because a ternary operator can become complex, especially
作为开发人员，我们将需要它，因为三元运算符可能会变得复杂，尤其是
if it includes checks – such as instanceof or null for a variable.
如果包含检查–例如instanceof或变量的null。
In such cases, IntelliJ IDEA can help you extract a variable and also replace the ternary
在这种情况下，IntelliJ IDEA可以帮助您提取变量并替换三元
operator with an if statement.
带有if语句的运算符。
Besides modiying the name of the extracted variable here, the real value of this extraction
除了在此处修改提取变量的名称外，此提取的实际值
lies in how you could modify it further in your code.
在于如何在代码中进一步对其进行修改。
Automatic refactoring is not a magic bullet.
自动重构不是万能的。
To use variable refactoring in IntelliJ IDEA effectively, you must know when it works safely
为了有效地在IntelliJ IDEA中使用变量重构，您必须知道它何时安全运行
and when you need to exercise caution.
以及何时需要谨慎。
Let's understand it using this code.
让我们用这段代码来理解它。
Before I refactor, let's quickly execute and see the output.
在重构之前，让我们快速执行并查看输出。
Here it is.
这里是。
Now, let me extract emp.title into a new variable and replace all its occurrences.
现在，让我将emp.title提取到新变量中并替换所有出现的变量。
It can output unexpected results because of the runnable here, which might execute before
由于此处可运行，它可能会输出意外的结果，该结果可能在执行之前
or after I call the log method.
或在我调用log方法之后。
And here'e the output of the modified code, which is not what we expected.
这是修改后的代码的输出，这不是我们期望的。
Let's work with another example.
让我们来看另一个例子。
When you extract a variable that includes a method call, IntelliJ IDEA let's you choose
当您提取包含方法调用的变量时，IntelliJ IDEA让您选择
whether you replace just one occurrence or all of them.
无论您仅替换一个事件还是全部替换。
Be careful in such cases.
在这种情况下要小心。
Such extraction may change your code behavior irrespective of whether the method called
这种提取可能会改变您的代码行为，而不管该方法是否调用
that you extract into a variable is pure or not.
您提取到变量中的内容是否纯净。
In this case, getTimeNow() was extracted to variable timeNow, which is used twice.
在这种情况下，将getTimeNow（）提取到变量timeNow中，该变量被使用了两次。
This code will always return value zero as the execution time - no matter how long the
该代码将始终返回零值作为执行时间-无论
loop takes to execute.
循环需要执行。
Before you get started with some serious refactoring of your code, please ensure you have an automated
在开始对代码进行认真的重构之前，请确保您具有自动
test suite set up to check all functionality is still the same after the modification.
修改后，要检查所有功能的测试套件设置仍然相同。
You can use IntelliJ IDEA to help you get started with defining unit tests.
您可以使用IntelliJ IDEA帮助您开始定义单元测试。
Happy refactoring and thanks for watching.
重构愉快，感谢您的观看。